. 。
.  。
Ouyang Yuchuan,
أويانغ يوتشوان ،
how can you compete with me?
كيف يمكنك ان تنافسني
Only you deserve my exclusive love.
أنت فقط تستحق حبي الحصري.
Darn your exclusive pet bunny.
الرتق الأرنب الخاص بك الحيوانات الأليفة الحصرية.
No matter what you say,
لا يهم ماتقوله،
It's just a little trick in my eyes.
إنها مجرد خدعة صغيرة في عيني.
Do you have to break us up?
هل عليك تفريقنا؟
I can't live without Miss Su,
لا أستطيع العيش بدون الآنسة سو ،
she doesn't like me because of money,
هي لا تحبني بسبب المال ،
I don't know what happened between us.
لا أعلم ماذا حدث بيننا.
But I'm sure she can't live without me.
لكنني متأكد من أنها لا تستطيع العيش بدوني.
Manager Wang,
مدير وانغ ،
why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Did you see Ouyang?
هل رأيت أويانغ؟
He said he was in a bad mood,
قال إنه كان في مزاج سيء ،
so he bought a flight ticket to Switzerland early in the morning.
لذلك اشترى تذكرة طيران إلى سويسرا في الصباح الباكر.
Did he say when he would come back?
هل قال متى سيعود؟
He said
هو قال
he wanted to leave this place.
أراد مغادرة هذا المكان.
Miss Su,
ملكة جمال سو ،
Mr. Su left alone.
غادر السيد سو وحده.
He wouldn't let me follow him.
لم يسمح لي بمتابعته.
You should also know about Stallone's heart.
يجب أن تعرف أيضًا عن قلب ستالون.
Old Master suffered
عانى السيد العجوز
the same pain back then.
نفس الألم في ذلك الوقت.
Actually, your choice is the best.
في الواقع ، اختيارك هو الأفضل.
At the very least,
على أقل تقدير،
nothing happened.
لم يحدث شيء.
I got it, Manager Wang.
لقد حصلت عليها ، المدير وانغ.
I'll make it clear to him when he comes back.
سأوضح له الأمر عندما يعود.
I won't let him suffer.
لن أتركه يعاني.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Shengnan,
شينغنان ،
bad news.
اخبار سيئة.
Ouyang's dog got stuck in the branch.
علق كلب أويانغ في الفرع.
Help me!
ساعدني!
It's coming out.
إنه يخرج.
He's out.
غادر.
Shengnan, thank you.
Shengnan ، شكرا لك.
Let's go back to the room.
دعنا نعود إلى الغرفة.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Shengnan,
شينغنان ،
thank you so much just now.
شكرا جزيلا الآن.
Come with me to save the dog.
تعال معي لإنقاذ الكلب.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
This is Ouyang Yuchuan's dog,
هذا كلب أويانغ يوتشوان ،
so I have to take care of him.
لذلك يجب أن أعتني به.
Later,
لاحقاً،
when he lands, we'll call him together.
عندما يهبط ، سنتصل به معًا.
Okay,
تمام،
I have a message for you,
لدي رسالة لك،
At 8: 00 this morning, TH9966 flight from this city to
الساعة 8:00 من هذا الصباح ، رحلة TH9966 من هذه المدينة إلى
Geneva suddenly lost control and skated off the runway about one
فقدت جنيف السيطرة فجأة وانزلقت عن المدرج بحوالي واحد
minute after taking off and taxiing at Dongshe
دقيقة بعد الإقلاع والتاكسي في Dongshe
Airport.
مطار.
Some passengers in the cabin were injured.
أصيب بعض الركاب في المقصورة.
Some flights at the airport are delayed.
تأخرت بعض الرحلات في المطار.
The cause of the accident is under further investigation.
سبب الحادث قيد مزيد من التحقيق.
Shengnan,
شينغنان ،
what's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Miss Su.
ملكة جمال سو.
-Fang Ye, drive faster. -Okay, Miss
-Fang Ye ، قد أسرع.  -حسنا يا آنسة
Su.
هم.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
The road ahead seems to be closed.
يبدو أن الطريق أمامنا مغلق.
What?
ماذا؟
Miss Su. Miss Su.
ملكة جمال سو.  ملكة جمال سو.
Ouyang Yuchuan
اويانغ يوتشوان
hugged me too tightly.
عانقني بشدة.
I can hardly breathe.
أنا بالكاد أستطيع التنفس.
I thought I would never see you again.
اعتقدت أنني لن أراك مرة أخرى.
I was already at the airport.
كنت بالفعل في المطار.
When I got my boarding pass, I found out that
عندما حصلت على بطاقة الصعود إلى الطائرة ، اكتشفت ذلك
I didn't know where I had put my ID.
لم أكن أعرف أين وضعت بطاقة هويتي.
How dare you say that?
كيف تجرؤ على أن تقول ذلك؟
As long as you're fine.
ما دمت بخير.
I told you to run around.
قلت لك أن تركض.
I used to think,
كنت أعتقد ان،
your love for me was all set.
حبك لي كان كل شيء.
So I can't accept it.
لذلك لا يمكنني قبوله.
But later,
ولكن في وقت لاحق،
I found out,
اكتشفت،
Actually, a set love
في الواقع ، مجموعة حب
counts as love, doesn't it?
يعتبر حب ، أليس كذلك؟
My love for Bunny
حبي من أجل الأرنب
will never change.
لن يتغير ابدا.
Like sunrise and sunset.
مثل شروق الشمس وغروبها.
The tide rises
المد يرتفع
and falls. Roar!
ويسقط.  هدير!
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
I've already returned your grandma's money.
لقد قمت بالفعل بإعادة أموال جدتك.
Little Rabbit, it's good that you didn't mention it,
الأرنب الصغير ، من الجيد أنك لم تذكر ذلك ،
but I get angry when you mention it.
لكني أغضب عندما تذكر ذلك.
Why did you take my grandma's money back then?
لماذا أخذت مال جدتي في ذلك الوقت؟
I can't believe you're still mad at me.
لا أصدق أنك ما زلت غاضبًا مني.
Of course I'm angry.
بالطبع أنا غاضب.
However,
لكن،
I won't be angry if you can correct your mistakes.
لن أغضب إذا تمكنت من تصحيح أخطائك.
I can't punish you less.
لا يمكنني معاقبتك أقل.
What punishment?
ما العقوبة؟
What's your name?
ما اسمك؟
White rabbit,
ارنب ابيض،
roar!
هدير!
What's your name?
ما اسمك؟
Ouyang Chuan Chuan,
أويانغ تشوان تشوان ،
Yes,
نعم،